Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran School of Art + Design records, circa 1908-2012 COR0009.0.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Student records, 1963-2001; Series 14
  - Diploma and certificate files, 1967-2001; Series 14 subseries 2
    - Tillery, Margie R. Diploma Comm. Design, 1969; Series 14 subseries 2 (Box 39, Folder 53)
    - Vrendenburg, Gay Ptg Diploma, 1969; Series 14 subseries 2 (Box 39, Folder 54)
    - A-D, circa 2000; Series 14 subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - F-H, circa 2000; Series 14 subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - I-L, circa 2000; Series 14 subseries 2 (Box 85, Folders 8-9)
    - M-S, circa 2000; Series 14 subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - T-Z, circa 2000; Series 14 subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Incompletes, 2001 Fall; Series 14 subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 27)
    - Mid-Semester Warnings, 2001 Spring; Series 14 subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 28)
    - Shows/Exhibition/Special Events, circa 2000; Series 14 subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 29)
    - Student records A-Z, circa 2000; Series 14 subseries 2 (Box 85, Folders 30-68)
- Financial records [legacy series], 1911-1939; Series 5
  Contains two volumes which record student entrance fee payments. They contain such data as "season" (fiscal year); payment date; student name; amount paid; total monies collected; and total number of students enrolled each term. Volume two contains this information for both the regular and the Saturday school beginning in 1936.
- Financial records, 1985-1999; Series 15
  Contains budget records for the Corcoran School of Art + Design transferred to the Corcoran Archives following initial the initial processing project of 1983.
  - Budget, 1968; Series 15 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - School Budget & YTD, Series 15 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Budget Objectives, Series 15 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Budget, Series 15 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Budget Background & Work Papers, Series 15 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Budget, Series 15 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Budget, Series 15 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Renee Kemp-Rotan Space Needs Assessment, Series 15 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - A Study of Finances & Faculty Salaries, Series 15 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Budget, Series 15 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - School Budget, Series 15 (Box 73, Folders 1-2)
  - School Budget, Series 15 (Box 73, Folders 3-4)
  - School Budget, Series 15 (Box 73, Folders 5-6)
  - School Budget, Series 15 (Box 73, Folders 7-8)
  - School Budget, Series 15 (Box 73, Folders 9-10)
  - School Budget, Series 15 (Box 73, Folders 11-12)
  - School Budget, Series 15 (Box 73, Folders 13-14)
- Andrews Memorial Association [legacy series], 1915-1916; Series 6
  Contains 25 letters of former pupils of the School's first Director, Eliphalet Frazer Andrews (1835-1915). The letters accompanied "subscriptions" (contributions) made to the Andrews Memorial Association which was formed in 1915 after Andrews' death. As a tribute to Andrews, the Association commissioned sculptor Richard E. Brooks (1865-1919) to produce a "memorial tablet to the late E.F. Andrews." The tablet, a 31"x25" bronze plaque, was accepted at the May 1917 Art School final exercises.
- Corcoran Alumni Club [legacy series], 1982-1983; Series 7
  Contains the club's constitution and by-laws, club brochure, membership cards, and club meeting announcements.
- Alumni, 1982-2012; Series 16
  Includes individual alumni records, class lists, correspondence, handbooks, memos, and select senior portfolios and publications. Materials date from 1982-2012.
  - Braustein, H. Terry, undated; Series 16 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Clopper, Jeff, undated; Series 16 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Davis, Gene, undated; Series 16 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Rooney, Mark, undated; Series 16 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Sarto, Elaine, undated; Series 16 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Shannon, Joe, undated; Series 16 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - 100 Marlin Agency, 1989; Series 16 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Dravec, Paula James, undated; Series 16 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Student Questionnaries Fall 1989, Series 16 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Hilda Witherspoon Painting Assemblage, 1992; Series 16 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Corcoran School of Art Annual Senior Exhibition 1987, Series 16 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1986 Portfolio/Scholarships, Series 16 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1983 Portfolio, Series 16 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1988 Senior Exhibition, Series 16 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1989 Senior Exhibition, Series 16 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1990 Senior Portfolio - Centennial, Series 16 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1991 Senior Portfolio, Series 16 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1992 Senior Portfolio, Series 16 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Corcoran Gallery of Art Annual Reports, 1983-1989; Series 16 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Marsh, Allan Thomas Dissertation "Washington's First Art Academy/The Corcoran School of Art 1875-1925", 1983; Series 16 (Box 31, Binder 20)
  - Alumni membership files, undated; Series 16 (Box 31, Card box 21)
  - Class of 1988 Senior Exhibition, Series 16 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Centennial Year Student Exhibition, 1990; Series 16 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - P.R., undated; Series 16 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Chron File, undated; Series 16 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Flyer, undated; Series 16 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Alumni List, 1993; Series 16 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Communication Arts, 1985 March-April; Series 16 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Stewart, Amy, undated; Series 16 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - KCAI Profile (Kansas City Art Institute), Summer 1992, vol. 1 no. 2, Series 16 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts, undated; Series 16 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - School of the Museum of Fine Arts, Boston, SMFA, undated; Series 16 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - School of the Museum of the Fine Arts Course Schedule, undated; Series 16 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Transcripts - Interviews, Panels, Etc., undated; Series 16 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Staff Meetings, undated; Series 16 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Spectrum, 1988; Series 16 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - RISD Views Vol. 1, 1989; Series 16 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - RISD Views Vol. 2, 1989-1990; Series 16 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - RISD Views Vol 3, 1990-1991; Series 16 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Alumni Involvement Ideas/Readings, undated; Series 16 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Lintas, undated; Series 16 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Laurie... FYI..., undated; Series 16 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Thanks you's, undated; Series 16 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Misc. memos, etc., undated; Series 16 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - 100 Convocation, 1990; Series 16 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Income for Circus cc: Pat Cooper, 1990; Series 16 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - 100 Committee, 1989-1990; Series 16 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - 100 100 100 100, 1988-1989; Series 16 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Letter from the Secretary of Education, 1990; Series 16 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - 100 Alumni, 1989-1990; Series 16 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Corcoran School of Art Catalogs, 1990-1991; Series 16 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Gala, 1990; Series 16 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Binney & Smith, 1989; Series 16 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Centennial Celebration - Accepts, 1990; Series 16 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Centennial Celebration - Regrets, 1990; Series 16 (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Misc. Centennial Info, undated; Series 16 (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Fish, John F. Aid, 1974-1975; Series 16 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - 100 Bills, etc., undated; Series 16 (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - ACE Consortium Edudisk Video Disk Project, 1986; Series 16 (Box 52, Binder 1)
  - Data Summary Higher Education Arts Data Services, 1988-1989; Series 16 (Box 52, Binder 2)
  - Data Summary Higher Education Arts Data Services, 1982-1983; Series 16 (Box 52, Binder 3)
  - ELIC, 1977-1980; Series 16 (Box 52, Binder 4)
  - National Association of Schools of Art and Design Workshop for Visiting Evaluators, circa 1980s; Series 16 (Box 52, Binder 5)
  - AICA Film Center Directory, circa 1980s; Series 16 (Box 52, Binder 6)
  - Higher Education ARts Data Services Data Summaries, circa 1980s; Series 16 (Box 52, Binder 7)
  - Alumni Steering Committee Guidelines, 1995; Series 16 (Box 136, Folder 17)
  - Alumni Association Exhibition Instituto de Arte Fotographico Lima, Peru, 1995; Series 16 (Box 136, Folder 18)
  - Second Hemicycle Show, 1995; Series 16 (Box 136, Folder 19)
  - Third Annual Corcoran Alumni Exhibition, 1994; Series 16 (Box 136, Folder 20)
  - Alumni Reception, 1994; Series 16 (Box 136, Folder 21)
  - Alumni Affairs Job Fair, 1994; Series 16 (Box 136, Folder 22)
  - VACOP, 1993-1995; Series 16 (Box 136, Folder 23)
  - The Corcoran Rag, 1993-1995; Series 16 (Box 136, Folder 24)
  - Alumni Assoc. Open Studio, 1993; Series 16 (Box 136, Folder 25)
  - Alumni Reception, 1993; Series 16 (Box 136, Folder 26)
  - Alumni Affairs Reception, 1992; Series 16 (Box 136, Folder 27)
  - First Hemicycle Show, 1992; Series 16 (Box 136, Folder 28)
  - Alumni Exhibition, 1991; Series 16 (Box 136, Folder 29)
  - Senior Bios, 2001; Series 16 (Box 160, Folder 1)
  - Senior Bios, 2000; Series 16 (Box 160, Folder 2)
  - Corcoran College of Art & Design First Annual Scholarship Luncheon/ Student Award Ceremony, 2005; Series 16 (Box 160, Folder 3)
  - Corcoran Alumni Exhibition Handbook, 2012; Series 16 (Box 160, Folder 4)
  - 25th BFA Anniversary Exhibition, 2005; Series 16 (Box 160, Folder 5)
  - Binder of Corcoran Publications, circa 1980s; Series 16 (Box 161, Folder 1)
  - Students, circa 1980s; Series 16 (Box 161, Folder 2)
  - Student Orientation, circa 1980s; Series 16 (Box 161, Folder 3)
  - Slides & Photos of Student Artwork, 1990s; Series 16 (Box 161, Folder 4)
  - Installation Shots, circa 1980s; Series 16 (Box 161, Folder 5)
  - Calfritz, circa 1980s; Series 16 (Box 161, Folder 6)
  - More Thesis Shows, Student Activities, Etc., 1980s; Series 16 (Box 161, Folder 7)
  - Thesis Shows, Student Activities, etc., circa 1980s; Series 16 (Box 161, Folder 8)
- Faculty association [legacy series], 1973-1981; Series 8
  Materials are arranged alphabetically by subject. Miscellaneous items appearing at the end of the series are arranged chronologically.
  Information on the Association for earlier years - its formation and activities - is located in the Dean Eugene Myers as well as the Dean Roy Slade records.
  Contains the Association's Constitution and By-laws; ballots; charts of faculty teaching hours; correspondence; course descriptions; meeting agendas; minutes, and notices; memoranda; and reports of the Faculty Association. Prominent subjects include the election of Association officers, the relationship between the Gallery Director and the School Dean, the appointment of Peter Marzio as Director, the Open Program, and Faculty sabbatical leave policies. The records show the Association's general concern with the role of the faculty in the School's decision-making processes.
  - American Association for Higher Education, Undated; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Beaux Arts Ball, Undated; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Brenner/Schwartz Meeting (With Faculty), Undated; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Ceramics Department - Space, Undated; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, Undated; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Curricula, 1981, Undated; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Curricula, Undated; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Dean/Director Relationship, Undated; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Faculty Evaluation Idea, Undated; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Faculty Newsletter, Undated; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Faculty Service Committee, Undated; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Five-Year Plan-School, Undated; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Jackson School Proposal, Undated; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Kreeger Letter (Re: Chief Executive Officer), Undated; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Library, Undated; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Peter Marzio, Undated; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Nomination - Association Elections, Undated; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Printmaking Department - Student Evaluation, Undated; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Qualifications of Dean - Suggestions, Undated; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Sabbatical Leave, Undated; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Saturday School Faculty, Undated; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Miscellaneous, 1973-1974; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Miscellaneous, 1977-1978; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Miscellaneous, 1980-1981; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Miscellaneous, Undated; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 58)
- School publications, 1908-2014; Series 9
  Contains brochures, catalogs, handbooks, leaflets, manuals, newsletters, newspapers, and portfolios (yearbooks).
  - Corcoran Art Journals, Undated; Series 9 (Box 14, Folders 1-17)
  - Portfolio, 1978; Series 9 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Portfolio, 1979; Series 9 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Portfolio, 1980; Series 9 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Portfolio, 1981; Series 9 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Portfolio, 1982; Series 9 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Portfolio, 1983; Series 9 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Portfolio, 1984; Series 9 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Portfolio, 1985; Series 9 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Portfolio, 1989; Series 9 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Portfolio, 1990; Series 9 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Senior Portfolio, 1991; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Senior Portfolio, 1992; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Senior Student Exhibitions and Sales - Promo Cards, Undated; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Art Scene, 1968; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Egg Plant, 1968-1969; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Aura, 1970; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Aura, 1971; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - School Newspaper, 1971-1972; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Korkoran, 1981; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Corcoran Free Press, 1981-1982; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Graphic Design Three, 1982; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Draw Wrinkle, 1983; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Last Chance Meal, 1983 November; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - High Contrast, 1984 Fall; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Corcoran Literary Magazine, N.D.; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Graphic Design Student, 2002; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Student Handbook, 1969-1970; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Student Handbook, 1973-1974; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Student Handbook, 1981-1982; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Student Orientation Packet, 1982-1983; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Student Handbook, 1982-1983; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Student Orientation Packet, 1983-1984; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Student Orientation Packet, 1984-1985; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Student Handbook, 1987-1988; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Student Handbook, 1989-1990; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Student Handbook, 1991-1992; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Student Handbook, 1993-1994; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Student Handbook, 1995-1996; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Student Handbook, 1996-1997; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Student Handbook, 1998-1999; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Student Handbook, 1999-2000; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Facebook, 2000-2001; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Student Handbook, 2000-2001; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Student Handbook, 2001-2002; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Student Handbook, 2003-2004; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Prospectus, 1908; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Prospectus, 1916-1917; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Prospectus, 1918-1919; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Prospectus, 1920-1921; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Prospectus, 1921-1922; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Prospectus, 1922-1923; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Prospectus, 1925-1926; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Prospectus, 1926-1927; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Prospectus, 1927-1928; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Prospectus, 1928-1929; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Prospectus, 1929-1930; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Prospectus, 1930-1931; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Prospectus, 1931-1932; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Prospectus, 1933-1934; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Prospectus, 1934-1935; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Prospectus, 1935-1936; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Prospectus, 1936-1937; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Catalog, 1937-1938; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Catalog, 1938-1939; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Catalog, 1939-1940; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Catalog, 1940-1941; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Catalog, 1941-1942; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Catalog, 1942-1943; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Catalog, 1943-1944; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Catalog, 1944-1945; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Catalog, 1946-1947; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Catalog, 1947-1948; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Announcement, 1948-1949; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Announcement, 1949-1950; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Announcement, 1950-1951; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Announcement, 1951-1952; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Catalog, 1952-1953; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Catalog, 1953-1954; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Catalog, 1954-1955; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Catalog, 1955-1956; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Catalog, 1956-1957; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Catalog, 1957-1958; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Catalog, 1958-1959; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Catalog, 1959-1960; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Catalog, 1960-1961; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Catalog, 1961-1962; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Catalog, 1962-1963; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Catalog, 1963-1964; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Catalog, 1964-1965; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Catalog, 1966-1967; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Catalog, 1967-1968; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Catalog, 1968-1969; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Catalog, 1969-1970; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Catalog, 1970-1971; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Catalog, 1971-1972; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Catalog, 1972-1973; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Catalog, 1973-1974; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Catalog, 1974-1975; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Catalog, 1975-1976; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Catalog, 1976-1977; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Catalog, 1977-1978; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Catalog, 1978-1979; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Catalog, 1979-1980; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Catalog, 1980-1981; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Catalog, 1981-1982; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Catalog, 1983-1984; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Catalog, 1984-1985; Series 9 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Catalog, 1985-1986; Series 9 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Catalog, 1986-1988; Series 9 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Catalog, 1989-1990; Series 9 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Catalog, 1990-1991; Series 9 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Catalog, 1991-1992; Series 9 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Catalog, 1993-1994; Series 9 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Catalog, 1994-1995; Series 9 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Catalog, 1995-1996; Series 9 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Catalog, 1996-1997; Series 9 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Catalog, 1997-1998; Series 9 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Catalog, 1998-1999; Series 9 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Catalog, 2000-2001; Series 9 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - D.C. A.D. Catalog, 2000-2001; Series 9 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Catalog, 2001-2002; Series 9 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Catalog, 2003; Series 9 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Catalog, 2004; Series 9 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - B.F.A. in Photojournalism, Undated; Series 9 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Announcement of M.A. Interior Design, 2004; Series 9 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - M.A. in Decorative Arts, Undated; Series 9 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - CSA Lectures, 1937-1949; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Landscape Classes, 1940; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Summer Program, 1950-1962; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Saturday School Events-Announcements & Invitations, 1964; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Summer School, 1964-1967; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Corcoran Abroad, 1968 Summer; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Summer School/Abroad, 1969; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Columbia, MD Program, 1969-1970; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Summer School/Abroad, 1970; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Summer School/Abroad, 1971; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Abroad, 1972 Summer; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Summer School, 1972; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Summer School, 1973; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Abroad, 1973 Summer; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Summer School, 1974; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Summer School, 1975; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Workshop in Maine, 1977; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Summer Program, 1978; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Summer Program, 1979; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Photography Program, 1979-1980; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Workshop in Maine, 1980; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Summer School, 1980; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Focus on Photojournalism, 2000 January/June; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Focus on Photojournalism, 2001 March; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Focus on Photojournalism, 2001 August; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Focus on Photojournalism, 2002 March; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - (C.E.) Camp Creativity, 2001 Summer; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Pre-College, 2002 June 30-July 13; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Camp Creativity, 2002 Summer; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Highschool: Focus on Photojournalism, 2002 July 21-27; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Camp Creativity, 2003; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Summer Study Abroad & Mem. Travel App, Undated; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Focus on Photojournalism, 2004; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Student Photojournalism Project, 2004 July 14-August 9; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Open Program, 1990 Spring; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Open Program, 1990 Summer; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Open Program, 1990 Fall; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Open Program, 1991 Spring; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Open Program, 1991 Summer; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Open Program, 1992 Spring; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Open Program, 1992 Summer; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Open Program, 1992 Fall; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Open Program, 1993 Fall; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Open Program, 1993 Spring; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Open Program, 1993 Summer; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Continuing Education, 1994; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Open Program, 1980-1981; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Summer School, 1981; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Open Program, 1981 Fall; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Open Program, 1982 Fall; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Open Program, 1982 Spring; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Open Program, 1982 Summer; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Open Program, 1983 Spring; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Open Program, 1983 Summer; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Open Program, 1983 Fall; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Open Program, 1984 Spring; Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Open Program, 1984 Summer; Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Open Program, 1984 Fall; Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Open Program, 1985 Spring; Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Open Program, 1985 Summer; Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Open Program, 1985 Fall; Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Open Program, 1986 Spring; Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Open Program, 1986 Summer; Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Open Program, 1986 Fall; Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Open Program, 1987 Spring; Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Open Program, 1987 Summer; Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Open Program, 1987 Fall; Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 12)